Jesús A. González L.

Web Developer

Buenos Aires, Argentina
jagltoro@gmail.com |+54 9 11 26579146
https://ar.linkedin.com/in/jagltoro

Summary

Ambitious problem solver with a passion for Web Development, who would like to join a team of like – minded developers.

Experience of creating logical and mind-sided solutions to problems. Responsible for my own personal development and continuously evaluating and upgrading my skills so that make me stay at the cutting edge of web development.

Skills

HTML
PHP
SQL
Javascript
Git

 Git

 Angular

 React

Languages

English Spanish

********* ****

Experience

MRM//MCCANN - Buenos Aires, Arg

05/2017 – Present

Web Developer Senior

Developer in several sites using AEM.

BLANCLINK - Caracas, Vzla

08/2016 - 12/2016

Web Developer

Developed frontend logic for a Retention Tool of a Call Center, using Angular.

Developed backend functionality with PHP 5.6 – 7 to create an API REST for an Android application.

Integrated the Technical Planning Committee to standardize front end technologies, stacks, tests and methodologies.

TERAVISION TECHNOLOGIES – Caracas, Vzla

01/2015 - 08/2016

Semi Senior - Web Developer

Jesus Gonzalez / RESUME P a g e | 2

Developed and maintain front-end and back-end functionality of websites.

Participated on meetings with clients to clarify what they want.

Designed prototypes for websites.

Developed an API REST to integrate an iOS application with their respective Database in SQL Server

Modified Javascript plugins to include or modify certain parts of their behavior so it can fit better in the project

PROSOFT SOLUTIONS – Caracas, Vzla

01/2014 - 01/2015

Software Specialist

Wrote modules to make appointments on their product.

Helped end users to solve operating problems.

Participated in brain storming sessions to come up with ideas.

Documented software and technical specifications.

THE FACTORY HKA – Caracas, Vzla

08/2013 - 12/2013

Web Developer

Developed the back-end management for the main page of the company Improvement and maintenance of websites operated by the company.

Education

UNIVERSIDAD "VALLE DEL MOMBOY" – Trujillo, Vzla

2012

Computer Engineering